Yan
Oh, yeah.
I know.
Oh, I love you too.
Hey, you say love me but kiss him.
이미너의심장은그의손을느끼고 Your heart has already felt the warmth of his palm
입맞추고속이고있어 kisses my lips and deceives me
전화를끊어도너의모습이보 고 고 hang up the phone or look at the 見妳
네가 '아냐아냐'해도결국엔너인걸 Even if you continue to deny you or you
내 사랑한너야 사랑한너야 I love you deeply
Oh baby. Tell me why you act so strange.
But tonight, I don't need a damn explain.
하지만이미난모두알고있었어, but I know all of them are clear.
Hey, you and the guy who is with you, I don’t need it.
Please come and disappear!
Sufficient to roll me with the happiness of the residue.
모두다 Bye Bye~ 사랑도 All are Bye Bye~ Love is also
모두다 Bye Bye~ 우정도 all are Bye Bye~ friendship is also
Feels like I'm ready (hey~!) No love I'm done with (woo~)
끝나버린사랑이라고해도말할필요없여 is the end of love, there is nothing to say, isn’t it?
모두다 Bye Bye 추억도 all Bye Bye~ memories are also
모두다bye Bye 슬픔도All are Bye Bye~ Even sadness is
Feels like I'm ready (hey~!) No love I'm done with (woo~)
끝나버린사이라고말해끝난거야Baby has ended the relationship has come to an end
Why do you kiss her?
친구의여자인걸알면서다가왔고 knows that a friend’s girlfriend is still approaching
감추고속이고있어 hides and deceives
I accidentally bumped into my sight and didn't evade my eyes.
네가 '아냐아냐'해도결국엔너인걸You keep denying whether or not you
Oh, I was convinced that you are not doubtful.
Oh baby. Tell me why you act so strange.
But tonight, I don't need a damn explain.
하지만이미난모두알고있었어, but I know all of them are clear.
Hey, you and the guy who is with you, I don’t need it.
Please come and disappear!
Sufficient to roll me with the happiness of the residue.
모두다 Bye Bye~ 사랑도 All are Bye Bye~ Love is also
모두다 Bye Bye~ 우정도 all are Bye Bye~ friendship is also
Feels like I'm ready (hey~!) No love I'm done with (woo~)
끝나버린사랑이라고해도말할필요없잖아 has ended the love is not nothing to say?
모두다 Bye Bye 추억도 all Bye Bye~ memories are also
모두다 Bye Bye 슬픔도 all Bye Bye~ Even sadness is also
Feels like I'm ready (hey~!) No love I'm done with (woo~)
끝나버린사이라고말해끝난거야Baby has ended the relationship has come to an end
모두다 Bye Bye~ all Bye Bye~
모두다 Bye Bye 추억도 all Bye Bye~ memories are also
모두다bye Bye 슬픔도All are Bye Bye~ Even sadness is
Feels like I'm ready (hey~!) No love I'm done with (woo~)
끝나버린사이라고말해끝난거야Baby has ended the relationship has come to an end
You'll never gonna find true love. Fxxk U
모두다 Bye Bye~ 사랑도 All are Bye Bye~ Love is also
모두다 Bye Bye~ 우정도 all are Bye Bye~ friendship is also
Feels like I'm ready (hey~!) No love I'm done with (woo~)
끝나버린사랑이라고해도말할필요없잖아 has ended the love is not nothing to say?
모두다 Bye Bye 추억도 all Bye Bye~ memories are also
모두다 Bye Bye 슬픔도 all Bye Bye~ Even sadness is also
Feels like I'm ready (hey~!) No love I'm done with (woo~)
The relationship that 끝나버린사이라고말해끝난거야 has ended has come to an end
이젠Goodbye on this Goodbye